Short-Run Student Publications UP215
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Short-Run Student Publications
1901 -- 2015
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
UP215
4.6 Linear Feet
1 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains short-lived student publications about various topics. Publications include political, cultural, religious, pre-professional and literary magazines.
- Short-Run Student Publications, 2015; UP215-001 (Box data_value_missing_f53ac26e919f02c8b398ad4034109e8c, Box 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
- Short-Run Student Publications, 1901 -- 2015; UP215.001; 4.6 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains short-lived student publications about various topics. Publications include political, cultural, religious, pre-professional and literary magazines.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Collective Effort: A Radical Tufts Journal, 1971 -- 1976; UP215.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Voyage, The Literary Magazine of the African-American Center, 1978; UP215.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Hakol, The Voice, 1980; UP215.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    The literary magazine of the Jewish Community of Tufts.
  - Recipes, 1971 -- 1972; UP215.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Squid Ink, 1975; UP215.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Good Shit, 1970; UP215.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Optometry Club Magazine, 1980; UP215.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Axon Press, 1980; UP215.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Out of the Ashes, 1975 -- 1977; UP215.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    Out of the Ashes is a Tufts feminist literary magazine. 1975 and 1977 issues were added from the Women's Center records (UA156) in May 2011.
  - Eritas, 1966; UP215.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Zings, 1972; UP215.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Class, 1972; UP215.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Cuzzy: An All-American Journal of Deviance, 1972; UP215.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Moosehead Press, 1979; UP215.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Bare Facts, 1987; UP215.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Pictorial Directory, 1958 -- 1965; UP215.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Jumbo Joins the Ivy League!?, 1972; UP215.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Let's Go, Walnut Hill, A Guide to Tufts, 1984; UP215.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Hollow Pillars, The Tufts Experience?, 1982; UP215.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    A publication of the Committee to Say What Needs to be Said.
  - The Pink Elephant Book, 1970; UP215.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - The Inside Track: The Tufts student guide to to course selection in the arts and sciences, 1983 -- 1984; UP215.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Course Evaluation, 1975; UP215.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Still Small Voice, 1990; UP215.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    Publication of the TUfts Christian Fellowship
  - The Student View, 1960; UP215.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Bocci, Lawn and Garden, 1998; UP215.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    Bocci, Lawn and Garden is the Tufts Magazine of queer literature and art.
  - Tufts Medics, October, 1901; UP215.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - The Gradgrind, 2001 -- 2002; UP215.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Water Rights, Poetry and Prose by Tufts Women Writers, compiled by Susan Meserve, May, 1995; UP215.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Mosaic, Tufts Journal of Multiracial and Interracial Relations, Spring, 2003; UP215.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    First Issue
  - The Greek Letter, spring, 2003; UP215.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - !!!MoFo!!!, 1996; UP215.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Resonance, 1995-02; UP215.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    Volume
    5
  - The Window, 1999 -- 2002; UP215.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
    This is the newsletter of Tufts Men Against Violence. Vol. 1/issue 1, vol. 3/issue 1, and vol. 4/issue 2 were moved to this collection from the Tufts Men Against Violence records UA218. Vol. 1/issue 1 was published under the title 'The Personalist Papers'.
  - A Certain Light, 2003; UP215.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Resonance, December, 1993; UP215.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Meridian, Spring, 1990; UP215.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Expressions, A publication of the Tufts Asian Students Club, 1986 -- 1987; UP215.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - MASSPIRG at Tufts: Public Interest Page, October, 1982; UP215.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - The Writer's Craft, 2003; UP215.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    Volume, issue
    1, 2
  - Cannon, Winter, 2004 -- 2005; UP215.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    1
  - Links, The Progressive Political Paper at Tufts, 1990; UP215.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    1, 1
  - Descript, Spring, 2005; UP215.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    A tongue-in-cheek look at the social side of Tufts
  - Tufts International Geographic, Fall, 2005; UP215.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    A forum for the international community at Tufts through articles, essays, prose, poetry, artwork and photography.
  - Tufts International Geographic, Spring, 2006; UP215.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
    2
  - The Senate Sentinel, 2005-11-01; UP215.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - The Senate Sentinel, 2006; UP215.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    Feb. 15 2006
  - Discourse, 2008; UP215.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - INfusion, February, 2009; UP215.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - InFusion, Spring, 2009; UP215.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Discourse, Spring, 2009; UP215.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
    Mission Statement: Dedicated to the power of reason and the exchange of ideas. A student publication in conjunction with The Institute for Global Leadership.
  - Discourse, Spring, 2010; UP215.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Freshman New Letter [Class of 1964], 1961; UP215.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
    Volume 1, No 1 from March 10, 1961 and Issue 2 from April 17, 1961.
  - Bound/Unbound: Tufts University Women's Journal, 1997; UP215.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
    Bound/Unbound was sponsored by the Women's Collective with the support of the Office of Women's Programs and the Department of Women's Studies.
  - Discourse, Spring, 2011; UP215.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Common Law: the Tufts Journal of Legal Affairs, 2011; UP215.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, 1984; UP215.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
    3, 1
  - The Connective Tissue, 2011-02; UP215.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - The Spectrum, 2010-12; UP215.001.002.00034; Asian American Alliance (Box 2)
    8, 1
  - RacEd, Spring, 2012; UP215.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
    Issue
  - TPS (Tufts Psychology Society) Report, 2003; UP215.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Today Tufts, Tomorrow the World!, 1979-04-30; UP215.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - The Recycled Paper, 1996-03; UP215.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
    2, 1
  - Child Development GSA Newsletter, Spring, 2007; UP215.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Justifiable Discrimination at Tufts: A History, 2012; UP215.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - El Tit, 2015; UP215.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
    Zines.
  - El Tit, 2015-04; UP215.001.002.00042 (Box data_value_missing_f53ac26e919f02c8b398ad4034109e8c, Box 2)
  - The Ivory Book, 2011 -- 2012; UP215.000075; 1 Digital Object(s); 701 Kilobytes